# Kathryn Werner

#### Education

Career Foundry
UX Immersion

University of Wisonsin Oshkosh

BFA - Graphic Design Minor - German

# **Tools**

Xd, Ai, In, Ps Sketch Figma Zepplin Salesforce Shopify

#### **Skills**

UI & UX User Research Graphic Design HTML CSS

# Contact

+1262.707.1688 wernerkat@gmail.com

### **Profile**

UI/UX designer with a background in textile production management. Proven experience using iterative techniques to brainstorm, test and implement visually captivating and customer focused design solutions. Accomplished in collaborating cross-functionally to understand and articulate design concepts with an empathetic approach.

# **Experience**

**UI & UX Designer** UX Bootcamp + Scholastic Book Fairs

November 2021 [Remote]

Took first place in a two-week long design challenge to design, brand and prototype a mobile app solving a key issue presented by Scholastic Books and Adobe

**Production Team Leader** Luckyleo Dancewear

June 2020 - Present [Denver, CO]

Managed a sewing production line and supported a team of seamstresses, designed digital tracking and communication systems, set goals and analyzed production outcomes

#### **Tier 1 Customer Support** Upserve

January 2018 - January 2019 [Denver, CO]

Acted as an advocate for customers while collaborating with engineers to ideate, test and implement solutions to technical issues in high volume environment via email, phone and chat

Graphic Designer Repairman App

October 2021 - February 2022 [Denver, CO]

Worked in tandem with founder and web developer in an early stage startup to create content of all digital campaigns leading up to mobile app launch